

Alireza Akrami

June 18th, 1989 akrami.alireza@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am a web developer with almost 8 years of experience which 4 years of that were on web security. I'm experienced in end-to-end development from server setup to design, development, and deployment. I'm seeking a position as a full-stack web developer or similar opportunity, where I can expand my technical knowledge and experience new challenges.

I have a good relationship with my colleagues, customers, and clients. I'm curious, flexible and self-starter with minimal supervision with good communication and cooperation.

SKILLS

- Web Development: PHP, Laravel, Symfony, NodeJS, ReactJS, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Sass
- Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis
- Linux: Basic Linux administration and Bash scripting
- Other: Docker, Git, Gitlab CI, API, Nginx, Python
- Soft Skills: Creativity, Responsibility, Teamwork, Time management,
 Communication, Problem solving, Tolerance and Patience

EXPERIENCE

BRTech, Tehran— Operations Team Leader

MAY 2019 - PRESENT

- Increased sale up to 150% by deploying a redundant system (increased throughput capacity)
- Developed and deployed an API sale channel next to current web and USSD dial channel
- Developed a reporting system written in PHP/Symfony language to manage and queue heavy loaded reports
- Trained, mentored and directed a team of 7 support engineers.

Technologies: PHP, Symfony, PostgreSQL, NodeJS, MongoDB, Linux, Redis

BRTech, Tehran— Technical Support Engineer

SEPTEMBER 2018 - MAY 2019

- Managed and maintained over 18 CentOS Linux servers
- Troubleshot services and programs
- Kept service availability up to 99.96%

Technologies: Linux, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis

Ansar Bank, Tehran — Web Security Specialist

MARCH 2014 - SEPTEMBER 2018

- Worked with many web vulnerabilities test applications such as WebInspect, ZAP, and SQLMap
- Developed web applications with Laravel to control the entry/exit of people to SOC/NOC
- Developed Python scripts for security purposes
- Maintained Fortiweb Web Firewall

Technologies: Linux, MongoDB, MySQL, PHP, Laravel, Python, Git, Continuous Integration, WebInspect, ZAP, SQLMap, and Many tools on Kali Linux.

Freelance— Web Full Stack Developer

2012 - PRESENT

- Design and develop websites and web apps with various technologies
- Develop scripts with python and nodejs for educational purposes
- Implement production environment for web applications
- Tune and Troubleshoot websites and web applications

Technologie: Linux, Redis, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, PHP, NodeJS, Laravel, Symfony, Python, Git, Gitlab-CI, MySQL

EDUCATION

K.N.Toosi University of Technology, Tehran — *M.Sc. Information Technology*

2012 - 2014

University of Isfahan, Isfahan — B.Sc. Information Technology

2007 - 2012

LANGUAGES

English: B2German: B1Persian: Native

PROFILES

My Website: https://iakrami.ir/en
 Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/iakrami
 Github: github.com/akrami
 Twitter: twitter.com/alirezatech